Resume

George Lukasin

ADDRESS Moscow, Russia EMAIL btsm0714@gmail.com SKYPE

live:.cid.ac1d41984a463590

I am a senior developer who gained more than Seven years of experience.

I'm a full-stack developer who specialized in everything. My core skills are C++, C#, python, OpenCV, Blockchain,Django, Laravel, Node.js, Vue, React, WebRTC,
WebGL ... etc. If you are looking for a full-stack developper who has the best programming skills and delivers
high quality sources in a short time, I would be your choice with no regrets.

The benefits you get by working with me:

You can find me online most of the time for communication, you will be able to see the progress of your project any time you need.

As I developer with my skills and experiences, I ensure you that you will get well structured, clean coded, and full comments in your project.

I provide full maintenance and troubleshooting for the projects.

I deliver all reports and documentations for the projects if needed.

My goal is to provide the best service for my customers. I have always doing my best and work full-time to satisfy my clients.

The most thing I value is trust.

Regards!

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Web Development Full-stack Engineer at Kyoto University Dev team.

April 2016 - January 2020

Team Leader at LIKEVR

April 2020 - March 2021

EDUCATION

Computer Science at Kyoto University

April 2010 - March 2016

Degree: Master

SKILLS

Cryptocurrency Exchange Platform Developing with C/C++, python ***** - Expert

JavaScript & Typescript (ES6/ES7)

**** - Expert

Node.js & MEAN & MERN Stack

**** - Expert

RESTful API

**** - Expert

HTML & CSS & SCSS

**** - Expert

PHP & LAMP

**** - Expert

React & Vue.js

**** - Expert

WORK RATE

\$20+ PER HOUR

\$6000+ PER MONTH